const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What is the term for a score one over par?',
      answers: [
        'Par',
        'Birdie',
        'Eagle',
        'Bogey'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Bogey'
    },
    {
     question: 'What is the penalty for hitting the ball out of bounds?',
      answers: [
        'No Penalty',
        'Disqualification',
        '1 Stroke Penalty',
        '2 Stroke Penalty',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '1 Stroke Penalty'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the difference between hazards marked by red and white stakes?',
      answers: [
        'There is no difference.',
        'Red hazards you must hit from the spot you last hit and add a stroke. White hazards you drop your ball as close to where the ball entered the hazard',
        'White hazards you must hit from the spot you last hit and add a stroke. Red hazards you drop your ball as close to where the ball entered the hazard',
        'You must drop where you last hit for both'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'White hazards you must hit from the spot you last hit and add a stroke. Red hazards you drop your ball as close to where the ball entered the hazard'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'When on the green, who hits first?',
      answers: [
        'Whoever is ready first',
        'The closest to the pin',
        'The farthest from the pin',
        'It doesn’t matter'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The farthest from the pin',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'How many clubs are you allowed to have in your bag?',
      answers: [
        '10',
        '12',
        '14',
        '8',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '14',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What does a red flag pin mean',
      answers: [
        'The pin is on the right',
        'The pin is on the back of the green',
        'The pin is on the back of the green',
        'The pin is on the front of the green',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The pin is on the front of the green',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'If a right handed golfer hits the ball and it tails left to right, what is it called?',
      answers: [
        'A fade or slice',
        'A draw or hook',
        'Nothing',
        'A duff',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A fade or slice',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'If your ball is on the green and another person hits your ball with their ball, what happens?',
      answers: [
        'You both receive 1 penalty stroke',
        'The other player receives a 2 stroke penalty.',
        'The other player is disqualified',
        'You receive a 2 stroke penalty',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'You receive a 2 stroke penalty',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'You score a 3 on a par 5, what is the correct term to describe your score?',
      answers: [
        'Par',
        'Eagle',
        'Birdie',
        'Bogey',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Eagle',
    },
  
   {
      question: 'Can you take a practice swing inside of a bunker?',
      answers: [
        'Yes, as long as you don’t ground your club',
        'No, you must swing outside of the bunker',
        'Yes, you can ground your club in the sand',
        'Yes, you can ground your club in fairway bunkers but not by the green.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes, as long as you don’t ground your club',
    }  
  ]
  
  
